JOHN CEDRICK MAGTIBAY

FREELANCE I. T. PRACTITIONER



1 0991-351-7798

johncedrick.magtibay01@gmail.com

Brgy 8. Lipa City, Batangas

PROFILE

A motivated freelancer with specialist expertise in I.T. Consultation, multimedia arts, system analysis, computer hardware servicing, and permit processing. A goal oriented and problem solver. Have a passion for helping others and giving them peace of mind specially in technology related concerns.

SKILLS

- · Design Thinking
- Graphic Designing
- Artificial Intelligence
- Software Development
- Problem-Solving
- Computer Literacy
- Hardware Troubleshooting
- Strong Communication

EXPERIENCE

I.T. SPECIALIST AND LIAISON OFFICER

Joel M. Raz and Associates CPA's

2019 - Present

- Handles All Technical Problems, maintain and manage Company Website.
- Deals with client inquiries related to business permits and BIR Registrations.
- Register Business to any Government Offices.

SYSTEM DEVELOPER AND I.T. SPECIALIST

ADROIT I.T. Solutions Inc.

2016 - 2019

- Design, conceptualize and develop programs and application.
- Provide solutions to Clients Concern related to any Technical problems

ACADEMIC TUTOR

BidaBest Tutorial Center

2015 - 2017

Teach Students Academic Subjects such as English, Mathematics,
Science, Filipino etc.

FREELANCE I.T. PRACTITIONER

2016-present

 Create Thesis projects related to Artificial Intelligence . Design and Print out Tarpaulin, Invitations, Business Cards and Tshirt Mocked ups. Computer Hardware Service Provider

EDUCATION

SECONDARY SCHOOL

Tipas National High School 2010 - 2014

BACHELOR OF SCIENCE IN COMPUTER SCIENCE

Kolehiyo ng Lungsod ng Lipa 2014 - 2020